Let's introduce a new string method that works with lists, join().
让我们介绍一个新的字符串方法 它将与列表 （list）和连接函数（join）一起进行
Join takes a list as an argument and returns a string
连接函数（join）将列表作为参数并返回一个字符串
consisting of the list elements joined by separator string.
具体来说 是通过一个字符串表示的分隔符将一个列表的元素连接在一起
In this example, we use a string,
在这个例子中 我们使用一个字符串反斜杠 "\"
backslash and as a separator,
并作为分隔符
so that there's a new line between each element, fore,
于是每个元素之间都有一条新的反斜杠线
new line, aft, new line,
fore new line aft new line
starboard, new line, port.
starboard new line port
We can also use other strings as separators with join.
我们也可以使用其他字符串作为连接的分隔符
Here, we use a hyphen.
在这里 我们使用连字符 "-"
It's important to remember to separate each of
重要的是要记住
the items in the list you're joining with a comma.
你需要在列表中用逗号吧列表中的每个元素隔开
Forgetting to do so will not trigger an error,
如果忘记这么做可能不会导致程序错误
but will also give you unexpected results.
但你也会得到非预期的结果
In the example below,
在下面的例子中
omitting a comma between Garcia and O'Kelley results in the following;
省略 Garcia 和 O'Kelley 之间的逗号将会导致如下结果：
Notice how the hyphen separator is missing between Garcia and O'Kelley,
请注意 Garcia 和 O'Kelley 之间缺少连字符表示的分隔符
and instead, the two strings were appended.
而不同的是 这两个字符串将会追加在一起
This happens because of Python's default string literal appending.
这是因为 Python 中 字符串会被默认文字追加
If join returns different results than expected,
如果连接（join）操作返回的结果与预期不同
check for missing commas.
检查是否缺少逗号
Also, note that join will trigger an error,
另请注意 连接（join）将触发的一个错误
if we tried to join anything other than strings.
如果我们尝试连接除字符串以外的任何东西
We get an error here because an integer was included in the lists.
我们在这里得到一个错误 因为列表中包含了一个整数
Lastly, a helpful method called append,
最后 一个名为追加（append）的有用的方法
adds an element to the end of the lists.
它将在列表末尾添加一个元素
Next, you'll practice working with lists and explore more list methods.
接下来 你将练习使用列表并探索更多列表方法